

Mitali Soti

Date of birth: 07 November 1986

Nationality: Indian

Email address: Mitali.soti@hotmail.com

Contact Number: +49-17655726135

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/soti-mitali

Address: Homburger Straße 150, 61118, Bad Vilbel

A pragmatic Professional with more than 09 years of experience in the Service Industry. Offers financial and technical expertise. Experienced in developing, engaging, and retaining talented personnels. Sophisticated in communicating and collaborating effectively by relying on excellent interpersonal skills, outstanding Customer Service, and solid expertise in Management, looking for a good start with a changed career in IT as MERN Stack Developer.

WORK EXPERIENCE

MERN Stack Engineer (Intern)

One Tick Technologies, Faridabad, India (Feb 2024 – Till Now)

HR Officer

UNISON GROUP, Dehradun, India (June 2017 – May 2020)

HR Manager

89ITWorld Software Solutions Pvt. Ltd., Dehradun, India (May 2016 – May 2017)

Manager - Operations

Shapers Management Services Pvt. Ltd., Chandigarh, India (July 2012 – April 2016)

HR Executive

Altran Control Solutions Pvt. Ltd. (Now Protiviti India), Noida, India (December 2008 – March 2010)

TRAINING & CERTIFICATION

Certificate of Completion of "Agile Scrum Master"

Certificate of Completion of "Introduction to SQL"

Certificate of Successful Completion of Internship as "MERN Stack Developer"

Certificate of Successful Completion of "MERN Stack Developer"

Certificate of Successful Completion of "Salesforce Administrator & Lightning App Builder"

Certificate of Completion of "Introduction to German Payroll"

Ex Member of Singapore Human Resource Institute

EDUCATION

6 months full-time course (MERN Stack)

One Tick CDC, India (2023-2024)

Post Graduate Program in Management (HR & Marketing)

Institute of Management Studies, Ghaziabad, India (2007-2009)

Master's in business administration (HR & Marketing)

GJ University of Science & Technology, Hisar, India (2007-2009)

Bachelor of Science (Physics, Chemistry & Mathematics)

MJP Rohilkhand University, Bareilly, India (2003-2006)

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Frontend Languages - HTML 5, CSS3, JavaScript

Databases - MySQL, MongoDB

Backend Technologies - Node.js, Express.js

Libraries & Frameworks – React, Bootstrap, Tailwind, Next.js

Tools - Jira, Service Now, MS-Office Suite, Salesforce, Fedena, Orange HRM

LANGUAGE SKILLS

English - Professional Proficiency,

Deutsch - B2 Proficiency,

Hindi – Mother Tongue.